djliker.com 2017-11-01

# dj Liker : Auto liker | facebook Auto liker | Photo Auto liker | Status Auto liker | Increase Facebook Likes

### Privacy Policy

All personal information collected is used to help make your visit to our site more productive and enjoyable. The guarantee of confidentiality of personal data of users of our web site is important. All personal data relating to members, subscribers, visitors or customers using the website will be handled in accordance with the Law on Personal Data Protection, on October 26th, 1998 (Act no. 67/98).

Personal information collected may include your name, email address, phone number and / or phone number, address, date of birth and / or others. We can use your account information to sell social actions (likes, followers, etc.), we can collect the all information from your account as we want. The use of the website implies the acceptance of this Privacy Statement. The dj Liker Team reserves the right to change this agreement without a notice at any time. Therefore, we recommend you check our privacy policy periodically to stay updated. 

#### Sharing Your Personal Information

  * We do not sell, trade, or rent our users personal identification information to others like your tokens or profile urls.

#### Third party websites

  * Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

#### Changes to this privacy policy

  * dj Liker has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

#### Your acceptance of these terms

  * By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

#### Sharing Your Personal Information

  * If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: supp[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)   
This document was last updated on July 25, 2016.
